I feel it stirrin' deep down inside my soul
我感觉在我的灵魂深处躁动不安
The rhythm's takin' hold
这节奏占据我的心
And it's about to roll
即将到来
A million sparkles falling across the floor
无数的光芒洒落在地板上
So DJ give it more
所以DJ给我更多
It's what we're looking for
这就是我们的期待
Dance the night away
彻夜舞蹈
All our friends right by our side
我们的朋友都在我们身边
It doesn't matter what style you bring
不管你穿什么风格
We're about to go on that ride
我们要踏上旅途
It's dance magic
这是舞蹈魔法
Once you have it
一旦你拥有
Let your body move
让你的身体动起来
Step in to the music
跟随音乐
It's dance magic
这是舞蹈魔法
And it's electric
令人兴奋
Let your body move to the music
让你的身体随着音乐动起来
Doesn't matter what style you've got
不管你有什么风格
Just keep dancin' on that spot
就在那里尽情舞蹈吧
Friends like you for who you are
像你这样的朋友才是真正的你
Dance queen on the scene superstar
舞王巨星登场
Crystal prep you've got the moves
准备好了你的舞步
Rainboom bringin' all the grooves
枪林弹雨带来美妙的旋律
Put 'em together and make 'em fit
把它们拼在一起让它们合得来
Crystal rainbooms dance magic
晶莹剔透的雨燕翩翩起舞
Dance the night away
彻夜舞蹈
All our friends right by our side
我们的朋友都在我们身边
It doesn't matter what style you bring
不管你穿什么风格
We're about to go on that ride
我们要踏上旅途
It's dance magic
这是舞蹈魔法
Once you have it
一旦你拥有
Let your body move step in to the music
让你的身体跟随音乐动起来
It's dance magic
这是舞蹈魔法
And it's electric
令人兴奋
Let your body move to the music
让你的身体随着音乐动起来
Crystal rainbooms got a style that's all their own
晶莹剔透的雨燕有自己独特的风格
Dancin' nonstop body movin' in the zone
不停歇地跳舞身体随心而动
Bring whatever style you've got
不管你有什么风格
Cuz the party is go in' on
因为派对还在继续
It's dance magic
这是舞蹈魔法
And it's electric
令人兴奋
Let your body move to the music
让你的身体随着音乐动起来